intrade.com 2012-11-14

# Privacy Policy

This policy relates to the privacy practice of Intrade in connection with the website www.Intrade.com. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites, including websites to which we may direct you from links on our website. 

## General Statement

Intrade respects your right to privacy and will not collect any personal information about you on this website other than for the purposes of registration, identification and the Services. No personal information is collected without your permission as set out in the Data Protection Consent and Exchange Rules. Any personal information that you provide to Intrade will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Act, 1988 of Ireland 

## Collection and Use of Technical Information

This website uses "cookies" to allow a User web browser (software used to read web pages) to recall those pages of this website which have already been visited by the User. Cookies are small pieces of information, placed on your computer by a website for tracking purposes. 

Technical information may be collected when you access this website, which may be logged by Intrade or our Internet service provider in order to determine statistical and other information regarding our website or the provision of the Services. The technical information is not personal information but may or may not personally identify you. The technical information is used so that we can monitor and improve our website. Such technical information may include:

Your IP address (the Internet protocol coded address for your computer which may uniquely identify your computer);  
Your domain server;  
Type of web browser (software used to read web pages);  
The top-level domain name used by you.

## Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information

We will only disclose your technical information or personal information where such disclosure is necessary to comply with a Court order or other legal process, to protect our rights, or our property, to enforce our Rules of Use, to operate our website and Services and to conduct, monitor and analyse the Service and Intrade business, to operate our security precautions, to obtain advice from Intrade' professional advisors, to carry on direct marketing by the agents of Intrade in relation to Intrade or other Persons, to assist any Person to whom Intrade proposes to transfer any of its rights and/or responsibilities, to comply with any legal or regulatory requirement of any jurisdiction, for registration for the Services and for providing the Services and any information in relation to the Services via the Internet, telephone and by any other means whatsoever, or as otherwise provided in the Rules.

## Lost or Stolen Information

If your personal information, i.e. your account number or password or credit card number, is lost, stolen or used without your permission, you should immediately notify Intrade. 

## Your Privacy

Intrade cannot ensure with websites other than this website, the security of your privacy or personal information or technical information which is given by you during any session or otherwise including websites to which the User may be directed by Intrade. 

## Updates and Changes to the Privacy Policy

Intrade reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such addition, change, update or modification on this website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective one week after notice is posted on the website. 

## Security Policy

Intrade have taken all reasonable precautions to prevent disclosure otherwise than as set out in this Privacy Policy or the Data Protection Consent and Exchange Rules of any of your personal information which you reveal to us on this website. To ensure the security of your credit card details, we use the Pay and Shop credit card management system. 

## Interpretation

Words and expressions defined in the Data Protection Consent and Exchange Rules shall where the context permits and unless otherwise defined herein, shall have the same meaning when used in this Privacy Policy.
